udthemes.com 2015-04-07

# Privacy Policy - UDTHEMES

This website uses cookies to log traffic and to help us provide you with a better website. By continuing to use the site you are agreeing to its use of cookies. [Read more.](http://udthemes.com/privacy/#cookies "Privacy") Close

policy

This privacy policy sets out how UDTHEMES uses and protects any information that you give UDTHEMES when you use the website.

UDTHEMES is committed to ensuring that your privacy is protected. Should we ask you to provide certain information by which you can be identified when using this website, then you can be assured that it will only be used in accordance with this privacy statement.

This privacy statement may change without prior notice. You should check this page from time to time to ensure that you are happy with any such changes. This policy is effective as of 01 October 2012.

## What we collect

  * contact information including email address
  * other information relevant to customer surveys and/or offers where specified

## How we use your information

We require this information to understand your needs and provide you with a better service, and in particular for the following reasons:

  * Internal record keeping.
  * We may use the information to improve our products and services.
  * We may periodically send promotional emails about new products, special offers or other information which we think you may find interesting using the email address which you have provided.
  * From time to time, we may also use your information to contact you for market research purposes. We may contact you by email, phone, fax or mail. We may use the information to customise the website according to your interests.

We will not sell, distribute or lease your personal information to third parties unless we have your consent or are required by law to do so.

If you believe that any information we are holding on you is incorrect or incomplete, please write to or email us at info@udthemes.com. We will promptly correct any information found to be incorrect.

## Security

We are committed to ensuring that your information is secure. In order to prevent unauthorised access or disclosure, we have put in place suitable physical, electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.

## External websites

Our website contains links to external websites of interest. However, once you have used these links to leave our site, you should note that we do not have any control over that other website.

Therefore, we cannot be held responsible for the protection and privacy of any information which you provide whilst visiting such sites and such sites are not governed by this privacy statement. You should exercise caution and look at the privacy statement applicable to the website in question.

## Cookies

A cookie is a small file which asks permission to be placed on your computer's hard drive. We use traffic log cookies to identify which pages are being used. This helps us analyse data about webpage traffic and improve our website in order to tailor it to customer needs. We only use this information for statistical analysis purposes and then the data is removed from the system.

Overall, cookies help us provide you with a better website. A cookie in no way gives us access to your computer or any information about you, other than the data you choose to share with us.

You can choose to accept or decline cookies. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. This may prevent you from taking full advantage of the website.
